## RAYAN BOUEZZEDINE

#### **PROFILE**

Motivated and well-disciplined Management Information System graduate. Seeking an entry level position to begin my career in a high-level professional environment, where I can utilize my skills and four years studies background to the maximum. I seek to work as a front-end developer to further my knowledge in this domain and utilize my skills. Have experience building, designing, implementing websites. Also experience in marketing, sales representative, and management.

#### EXPERIENCE

Website Developer, 01/2022 - Actuel Freelancer - Lebanon - Full Time Job

 Developing, optimizing and maintaining user-friendly websites using Front-end and Back-end languages, to meet my client needs and goals.

Sales Representative, 08/2021 - 08/2022

Ishop - Barouk, Lebanon - Full Time Job

- Assist process remittance transfers for clients (Western Union).
- Hardware and Software Installation for computers and mobiles.
- · Wireless Internet installation for clients.
- Understanding the business workflow to help identify process efficiencies.
- · Develop and support device frimware.

Customer Service, 06/2017 - 06/2019

Tourist Restaurant - Barouk, Lebanon - Summer Part
Time Job

- Personalized support for customers throughout their meal to offer them a pleasant experience.
- Anticipating customer's needs, and evaluating their satisfaction.

Customer Service, 04/2016 - 01/2020

Maakoulat Al Said - Lebanon - Part time Job

- Set up and coordinate a range of special events.
- Gathered together all food supplies, utensils, decorations, heating elements, and serving trays needed for each catering event.
- Worked with customers to ensure satisfaction in such areas as quality, service, and problem resolution.

#### EDUCATION

Lebanese University, 12/2021 - 11/2022

Master of Science (M.S.) - Management Information system

Aley, Lebanon

Lebanese University, 10/2018 - 11/2021

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) - Management Information system

Aley, Lebanon



#### CONTACT

0

Beirut, Lebanon



(961) 71 520 182



rayan.bouezzedine13@gm ail.com

#### SKILLS

- · Expert in: Html, CSS
- Intermediate in: JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, REACT.JS, PHP, MYSQL, WORDPRESS
- Basic in: NODE.JS, PYTHON, BOOTSTRAP, DJANGO, WAGTAIL, ANGULAR.JS, JAVA, C++, C#

### LANGUAGES =

Arabic :

Native language

English

Fluent

French

Beginner

# LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

- The Ultimate 2023 Full stack Web Development Bootcamp Udemy-2023
- Artificial Intelligence
   Centre MINE-2022
- Emotional Intelligence
   Centre MINE 2022
- Your mission, Your purpose
   Centre MINE 2022
- · Latest Trends in

Cybersecurity

Centre MINE - 2022

 Communication and Public Relations

Centre MINE - 2022